<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Managed Services Status - Mad Scientist Technologies</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Managed Services Status - Mad Scientist Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:16:04 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DMARC Implementation Project</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/dmarc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 14:16:04 -0500</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/dmarc/</guid>
      <description>Project Status: In Progress (Partially Completed)&#xA;Client Domains: Current: Monitoring DMARC Reports Changing: April 15-20 Monitoring + Quartintine Goal/Additional Information The Implementation of DMARC Standard/Records (DMARC, DKIM, SPF) for all email messaging services managed by Mad Scientist Technologies.&#xA;Additional information about DMARC, DKIM, and SPF can be found on the original project page.&#xA;Questions about this project, contact us.&#xA;Project Time Last Updated: April 2024&#xA;Managed Domains - Clients SPF/DKIM Status Completed/Fully Implemented DMARC Status Records Implemented Status: Monitoring Message Percentage: 100% Disposition on Failing Messages: None We will start moving managed domains to the next step, Quarantine, during the month of April 2024.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Implementation of SPF, DKIM, and DMARC for Managed Mail Services</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/original-dmarc-outline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/original-dmarc-outline/</guid>
      <description>Project Status: In Progress / Partial Delay&#xA;Last Update: August 27, 2016&#xA;The timeline for this project has slipped due to the more pressing issue of mail delivery issues to Outlook.com/Hotmail.com/Live.com.&#xA;The timeline below will need to be re-evaluated due this delay. However we are happy to report that the majority of our Managed Mail Only Clients have been completely migrated to a full SPF, DKIM and DMARC Implementation. We are still monitoring the DMARC reports for problems before implementing the Quarantine and Reject functionality.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
